life-answers.com 2012-09-19

# Free Numerology Readings, Reports & Horoscopes | Life-Answers.com

The information and data contained on and through the Numerogy areas of the Life-Answers.com Web site is to be treated purely for your entertainment purposes only. Any prediction or other message that you receive is not a substitute for advice, programs, or treatment that you would normally receive from a licensed professional such as a lawyer, doctor, psychiatrist, or financial advisor. Accordingly, Life-Answers.com provides no guarantees, implied warranties, or assurances of any kind, and will not be responsible for any interpretation made or use by the recipient of the information and data mentioned above.

**Privacy Statement**

Privacy Policy

Welcome to Life-Answers.com - the number one site in the world for Numerology. We are happy to provide services to you based on the following conditions.

Privacy 

Please read over this Privacy Policy, which also governs your visit to Life-Answers.com. 

At Life-Answers.com, one of our top priorities is making sure that the information we have about you is protected and secure. 

We value our relationship with you and work hard to preserve your privacy. We do collect personal information to allow us to personalize Horoscopes, Numerology and Numerology reports. We regard all personal information - including birth data - as completely confidential, and will not divulge your information to any third party.

Information Collection & Use

In order to receive any free or paid reports, daily forecast or other products we provide, you must first complete an order form. When ordering you will need to make certain entries (such as name, birth date and email address) so we can contact you about periodic updates on various matters in which you've expressed an interest, like: events that may impact your life, exclusive opportunities, referrals, and discounts on materials that will help you make the most out of your life.

Life-Answers.com is the sole owner of the information collected on Life-Answers.com.

If you purchase a product or service from Life-Answers.com, you will need to fill in certain personal information on your order form. You will need to fill in contact entries (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial entries (such as credit card number, expiration date.) Life-Answers.com uses these items for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If there is any problem in processing an order, Life-Answers.com will contact you.

Use of Entries 

The entries you fill out on your order forms are used to calculate your Numerology report and/or to provide you with a daily forecast that is personally relevant to you because it is specifically based on your birth information. The entries are also used to identify upcoming events and subjects that may interest or affect you, so we can let you know about them and any opportunities or actions you can take to make the most of conditions and chances to improve your life.

**Communications from Life-Answers.com**

Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on exclusive opportunities, referrals, and discounts on materials that will help you make the most of the current conditions as they arise.

You can always choose not to receive these types of communications. See 'Choice/Opt-out' below.

Customer Service 

Based upon the entries you provide in the forecast registration and order forms, Life-Answers.com may send you a confirmation email to verify your order. Life-Answers.com will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you only via email.

Profile 

Life-Answers.com stores the material collected through order forms, log files and third party sources to create a "profile" of your preferences. Life-Answers.com ties your personal entries and your purchasing history to the profile, in order to provide opportunities, updates, offers tailored specifically to fulfill your individual needs and to improve the content of your daily Forecast, other email updates, and the resources presented on Life-Answers.com. 

Life-Answers.com does not share your profile with other third parties.

Agents 

Life-Answers.com uses a credit card processing company and/or PayPal to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable entries and materials for any other purpose. 

Legal Disclaimer

Life-Answers.com reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable entries and materials as required by law and when Life-Answers.com believes that disclosure is necessary to protect its rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

Choice/Opt-out

If you no longer wish to receive your daily Forecast or exclusive opportunities for offers and discounts or important updates and how they'll affect you, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each forecast or email letter or at 'Contact Us' link.

Other Files 

Life-Answers.com gathers certain data automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp.

Life-Answers.com uses this data, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer Life-Answers.com, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about subscribers as a whole.

Life-Answers.com does link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable entries in order to determine your country of residence for customs and shipping purposes. 

Cookies 

Life-Answers.com does not use cookies on its site except for your daily forecast which is on our home page and only when you have opted to use this feature. This allows us to provide you with your daily forecast each day without you having to re-input your information. 

Links to Other Sites 

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Life-Answers.com . Please be aware that Life-Answers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by Life-Answers.com.

Access to Personal Information 

If your personally identifiable entries change, or if you no longer desire your daily Forecast or emails about opportunities, updates, offers tailored specifically to fulfill your individual needs, you may correct, update, delete or unsubscribe.

Security 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on any order forms, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Life-Answers.com follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal entries you provide, both during transmission and once Life-Answers.com receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while Life-Answers.com strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal entries, Life-Answers.com cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on this Web site, you can email us at our 'Contact Us' link or by mail at,  
Life Answers  
PO Box 802536  
Dallas, TX 75380-2536  
USA

Changes to this Privacy Statement 

If Life-Answers.com changes this privacy policy, Life-Answers.com will post those changes to this privacy statement. Life-Answers.com reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. 

Children's Privacy 

Our Company Commitment to Children's Privacy: Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen years or older. 

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILD ONLINE PRIVACY ACT (COPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO. 

LATEST UPDATE

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: January 18, 2008. Contact Us If you have any questions or concerns that you feel weren’t addressed herein, please contact us at our 'Contact Us' link. 

**All Rights Reserved.**

This Website and all of its contents are protected by copyright laws and/or trademarks or other laws. No part may be reproduced, stored in a retrieval system, or transmitted in any form or by any means, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or otherwise, without the written permission of Life-Answers.com. 

This Terms & Conditions Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between You and us and governs your use of the Service, superseding any prior agreements between You and us with respect to the Service.
